Rohan-sensei!
Thanks for meeting up with me.
It's a beautiful day, isn't it?
What's that book you're reading there?
Uh, the Steel Collection.
Death Steel?
Is that a new rock band or something?
He was a Russian-born artist.
I believe he died in 1955.
By the way, Kaigamori,
I know full well that in
the working world at large,
being late for any business
meeting is considered improper.
However,
an editor arriving six minutes early for a
meeting with his manga
artist is equally rude,
don't you think?
Oh, I'm so sorry about that.
Arriving early is a bad thing, then?
You're lucky you're meeting with me.
But on to business.
You want to talk about my upcoming
61-page one-shot manga, no?
Excuse me, Rohan-sensei.
We're huge friggin' fans!
Can we please get your autograph?
Can you make mine out to my
pal Akira? Cut it out! Mr.
Kishibe's not giving autographs.
Can you see he's hard at work?
He doesn't have time!
It's already done.
Unlike some manga artists,
I'm a fast worker.
I always have time to thank my fans.
Two-trip-part autographs done in
coffee?! No way! Thank you, sir!
We'll treasure these!
Actually, if you wouldn't mind?
There is something personal
I'd like to discuss.
before we get down to business.
Sure.
To be perfectly frank,
it's a question about cash.
More specifically, my payment.
All right?
Could you pay me in advance?
I've actually just gone bankrupt.
What?
I haven't gone into debt yet, but...
right now, I'm homeless.
I'm staying at Koichi's at the moment,
but I don't even have a desk to work on.
My Sailor Moon figures, Led Zeppelin
paper jacket CDs, Rurouni Kenshin manga.
I've sold them all.
Slow down a sec!
You don't have anywhere to work?
And bankrupt?
Didn't you just buy yourself an
entire mountain the other day,
complete with vacation cottages?
I told you before,
I bought it to investigate
the rumors of the
monster that lives on
that hill for my manga.
But then I heard those developer bastards
wanted to build a resort up there.
So I bought the six surrounding hills to
put a stop to their sleazy little plan.
More land equaled more influence,
so what else was I to do?
I bought it all to stop the construction.
But with plans for the resort
canceled, the land's value plummeted.
Now that area's just wilderness
in the middle of nowhere.
The six hills I just bought
are basically all worthless.
Which means I'm flat broke.
Do you think you could
offer me in advance?
Let me process all this.
Did you really buy all those hills
solely for manga research purposes?
Yeah.
Not as an investment?
That's correct.
I'm shooting for reality here.
In your comic about a
folktale monster on a hill?
You heard me.
Imagine if they did build the resort.
All that traffic could have
scared the monster elsewhere.
In which case, my plan
would be for naught.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's with that face?
Can't you look me in the eye?
Hey, you're looking away.
Hey, you think that I've gone
completely off my rocker, don't you, Mr.
Editor? Listen up.
Souped-up supercars and basement video
game theaters are fine and dandy,
but they're not the only
things manga artists can buy.
Hmph.
And what's more, I did find it in the end.
So you see, my research
was worth every yen.
Listen carefully,
and don't tell anyone outside the
magazine what I'm about to tell you.
You found it? What?
What exactly are you saying you found?
Oh, come now.
Do you not listen to
people when they talk?
I saw it with my own eyes.
The monster of Mutsukabe Hill does exist.
And as of this moment,
it lives there still.
I hate to ask, Rohan-sensei, but
could you please say that again?
What lives there?
There was a girl named Naoko Osato, a
student in her last year of college.
But as September came to a close,
she would murder her boyfriend.
Thank you.
Naoko Osato,
the only daughter of the Osato family,
who found their fortune making Masa in
Mutskabe village for over 300 years.
The Osato estate stood at the end
of a single track road upon a hill,
which is to say, the The
entire hill was theirs.
Hey, could you go home for the day? Huh?
And clean up the game stuff, will you?
What's going on?
Someone from the main
house coming to visit?
Does it matter?
You can leave through the back.
Come on, now.
Lately, you've been, I don't
know, kind of chilly toward me?
I don't want to ask this,
but is there another guy?
You just spared me the
trouble of an explanation.
Look, I'm not going to deny that
we've had some good times together,
but it's not going to work out
as long as my dad's around.
You're a part-time gardener.
And as my dad's only daughter, I'm
supposed to protect the family fortune.
We're done.
I Don't think so?
You don't mean that come on.
What's wrong with keeping our thing going?
There's no reason for us to split up
How do you think they would
react if they came in and saw
us like this your precious
father in this new man of yours?
Let me fucking go!
You...
you bitch!
I'm sorry.
I didn't...
after you hit me, I just reacted.
I really do love you now.
I mean, even if we have to keep it
secret, I'm happy just the way things...
Go on!
Get out of here! Please,
now. Listen... Go!
Take the damn money and go home already!
Well, we didn't exactly tell
her we were coming, did we?
She'll probably be flustered.
Bet she'll try to do
herself up in record time.
I'll be at the door any minute.
Gunpei, please take your
stuff and get out of here now.
To be perfectly honest, you're
the one I want to be with.
But this is the man I've been engaged to.
My family has decided that we'll be
getting married after I graduate college.
So this is the end for us.
We can't see each other anymore.
Gunpei?
Hey.
No.
If this is another one of
your jokes, it's not funny.
Another prank, right? Gunpei.
Stop playing around.
I don't feel a pulse. He's...
He's dead.
Not knowing what else to do, Naoko Osato
decided to dress Gunpei's wound regardless.
She pressed a towel she found
nearby against his head.
This has to be some kind of trick.
It can't be true.
I just gave him a little push.
Why was that golf club there?
Why?
This makes it look like...
Like I...
This makes it look like I took the
golf club and beat him to death!
Gunpei.
What should I do?
A doctor.
I'll call a doctor.
But if he's dead already,
I'll let doctor be any help.
Oh god, do I have to
call the cops instead?
Naoko, are you in there?
It's me, dad.
And I brought Shuichi along with me.
He's sure excited to see you.
No, I'm not here.
I'm not anywhere at all.
Huh. It's locked. Hmm.
Maybe Naoko isn't here after all.
It may have been my imagination, Mr.
Osato, but I could have sworn I saw
that window screen move earlier.
I need to do something with his body.
What's going on he
doesn't have a pulse his
heart's not beating so
why is he still bleeding?
Naoko, are you there?
What's going on?
Are you alright?
I've got a spare key.
Let's open the door.
Oh, father!
I didn't hear you.
You caught me tidying up in the kitchen.
Ah, so you are home.
Guess who's here. Shuichi.
Really?
How wonderful.
Could you ask him to wait
for me in the main house?
Naoko, your voice sounds a little off.
Are you alright? Do you
need a hand? No, I'm okay.
Just changing into something nicer.
So please don't open the door.
I'll be with you in a minute, promise.
Please don't open that door!
What the hell is happening?
How is it even possible for humans to keep
bleeding like this after they're dead?
Naoko, you're using an awful lot of water.
What are you up to?
It's me, Shuichi.
I bet you're wondering what
I'm still doing out front here.
Honestly, it was your father's idea.
He lent me the spare key so you and I
could spend more quality time together.
No! Damn!
You can't come in no matter what!
Naoko, I actually saw someone.
A figure in the window as I
was approaching the house.
It looked like someone
was in there with you.
Are you alone in there right now?
Well, I could have sworn that I saw
one other person in the house with you.
I'm sorry.
But this is all your fault anyway.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Naoko, are you all right?
So there is someone else in there.
Gunpei, please!
Stop bleeding, you have to stop!
That's it, I'm coming in right now!
You mentioned you saw
someone else in here with me?
Who might that have been, Suichi?
Please...
Please stop...
Unpei... I'm sorry...
Stop.
Please forgive me.
Hey, I'm really sorry about that.
Talk about an overactive imagination.
I'll go join your father in the
main house until you're ready.
And so, as arranged,
Naoko was married the next spring, and
Shuichi was welcomed into the Osato family.
But ever since that day, Gunpei Kamafsa
has never once stopped bleeding.
Every day, he quietly
bleeds about 300 cc's.
If his body is not moved, he
will never bleed more than that.
However, the bleeding is continuous.
Despite the fact that any and all signs
of life have completely disappeared.
Naoko Osato has never once been on a
trip away from home since her marriage.
And every morning...
She takes a glass bottle full of Gunpei's
blood and discreetly discards it.
A daily ritual.
She does this without fail so as to hide
it from the prying eyes of her family.
Hey Naoko, come and eat with us.
I'll be right there.
Ever since the detached guest house
was demolished for conversion.
Hidden in the attic above
the closet in the main house.
Lies Gunpei.
This is where Naoko discovered.
That whenever she sprayed
water All over Gunpei's body
Somehow his skin would temporarily return
to the state it was in when he was alive.
You're so cute when you're asleep.
Gunpei, you are mine and mine alone.
I'm the only person in the whole world who
could take care of you forever and ever?
What exactly is he?
There's no denying he's
been dead this entire time
I first learned of Gunpei Kamofsa
on one of my trips to the area.
His name arose while I was
talking to some Mutskabe villagers
about their stories and long-held
beliefs in local monsters.
So, you see, Mr. Kishibe,
this is an absolutely positively fantastic,
profitable, and lucrative deal for you.
Absolutely not.
I've told you a hundred times
I'm not selling my hills.
Well, I'm sure there's some way
we can help change your mind.
Heh heh heh. Huh?
Oh!
Yes, hello, this is Matsudera.
I learned of this affair when I stumbled
into a chance encounter with Naoko Osato,
and read her memory with Heaven's Door.
It's through this stroke of luck that I
learned about the existence of this man.
Yes, huh, hey can you hear me?
The signal's bad, just a moment please.
So, what are you?
Huh, Gunpei?
I intend to see the truth
with my own two eyes.
I want to know what you're after.
In the attic above the closet in
that main house, I'll find him there.
You're Rohan Kishibe, aren't you?
The manga artist.
That's what I thought.
I'd heard you'd been
snooping around here lately.
Who are you?
Not to talk to strange
men apparently there are
a lot of perverts and
weirdos around these days.
Wait what are you.
Hey are you all right what was all
that about running off like that.
She's dead.
What happened?
It can't be.
It's absurd. Ridiculous.
This makes it look like...
It looks like I was responsible
for this poor girl's death.
What's going on here?
Who the hell is this girl?
It can't be.
There's no way.
Is this girl Gunpei's child?
Naoko Osato,
did she get pregnant from the corpse
hiding in the attic and give birth? Mr.
Koshime, where are you?
Where are you, Mr. Koshime?
Damn it.
It's trying to possess me.
Heaven's door!
This is bad.
All the memories that make this girl
who she is, they're fading away.
No, no!
It's all disappearing!
If her memories go, I
can't bring her back!
So before that...
Mom!
I'm hungry!
That was too close for comfort.
A moment's hesitation, and
I could have been possessed.
Or worse yet, devastated.
What a terrifying
creature. Another second.
So that's where you went, Mr.
Kishibe.
Terribly sorry to have
left you alone like that.
It was an important call from
the main office, you see.
You can take your offer and shove it.
What?!
This was the very monster I sought.
I'll call it the Monster of Mutskabe Hill.
I don't know how long
this monster has existed.
Perhaps forever.
It preys on love and the
human heart's weakness.
In doing so, it makes
humans do everything for it.
It doesn't work, takes no
responsibility, and suffers no hardship.
This monster's sole
purpose is to reproduce.
No, perhaps I should call it an organism.
The greatest moment of this creature's
life is when it dies in front of someone.
I do think that it's possible more of
these creatures are out there somewhere.
They may prolong their existence by
finding a victim to die in front of.
Is that really a true story?
It's a hard pill to swallow.
Even so, there's no way
that story's a complete lie.
Have you heard of this monster?
Yes,
I do remember a similar creature that
made its home among the Magellanic Clouds.
Listen up, you kids.
You can't just barge into our...
By the way, there's something
I've always wanted to ask you.
Are you serious when
you say you're an alien?
Oh, yes.
I traveled from the Magellanic
Clouds to live here in Mariah.
But my spaceship is still standing by...
All this alien crap is
putting me to sleep here.
How many Mutsukabe Hill
Monsters walk this world?
I have no interest in questions like that.
Naoko Osato looks happy enough.
And I've discovered the monster's purpose!
I know what I am.
And it's not a scholar.
Or a journalist either.
Me.
I'm just a manga artist.
Mom!
Do you think I'll marry
a handsome man one day?
Of course you will.
I don't want to know the truth.
Of life that never melts.
To chain a mystic rise.
I'm coming,
I'm on my way to find
eternal valedictives!
Exploding all their
tears, drops by the sun.
I can feel my heart beating,
I can see my faith.
All spinning round beyond our time.
Rise up to the sky like a butterfly.
Show me what's inside your world.
Shining stars will guide
me to somewhere high.
Finding the truth beyond
the heaven's door.
You
Thank you.